WANATCHAPORN CHURVIVAT

Software Developer

Contact

- +6699-020-3144
- www.proywanat.dev
- proywanat@gmail.com
- github.com/proywanat

Profile

My name is Wanat. I am a Software Developer with 1 year of experience in developing and maintaining web and mobile applications. I have aptitude in various programming languages and frameworks such as ReactJS, Java, and Flutter to deliver the best results that meet user needs.

Skill

Programming

- C C++
- PostgreSQL SQLite

Web Development

- HTML PHP CSS
 JavaScript
- React (JavaScript/TypeScript)
- Next.js Redux
- AngularNode.js/Express.js
- Java SpringBoot

Application Development

- Flutter/Java
- Firebase

Data Engineering

• Python SQL

7 Other

- Git AWS MongoDB
- API Messaging

Language

- Thai (Native)
- English

Education

Bachelor of Science (Computer Science) King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok | 2019 - 2023

GPAX: 2.77

Work Experience

T-ECOSYS Co.,Ltd. Software Developer

Dec 2023 - Present

- Industrial Digital Platform (iDP) Project: Handled website translation, bug fixes with international teams, and feature development using Next.js (TypeScript) and Spring Boot.
- iDP Ecommerce Project: Tasked with designing an industrial e-commerce website using WordPress and develop the main iDP website to ensure seamless connectivity between the two platforms.
- Developed search products API with Spring Boot and used data from mongodb.

JENOSIZE Co.,Ltd. Full Stack Engineer

Jul 2023 - Nov 2023

- Marketing Cloud Project: Developed new features based on client needs such as CRM management, Live Chat enhancements, and Automate Flows. Key clients include CP ALL (7-Eleven) and Big C.
- 7Chat&Shop Project: Built an ordering system via LINE for CP ALL (7-Eleven), and collaborated closely on issue resolution with clients and QA.
- Live Chat System (PF Project): Created a property chat system for Property Perfect, including message-counting APIs and push notification setup via OneSignal for iOS and Android.